S. M Hadi

Fontend Developer

CONTACT

Phone
+8801571208830

Email s.mhadi.up@gmail.com

Address

Dhaka, Bangladesh

EDUCATION

BSc in CSE
2023 to recent

Higher Secondary
2020 to 2022

Secondary Exam

LANGUAGE

EnglishBanglaHindi



ABOUT ME

Hi, I am S. M Hadi. I am a passionate web developer with 1 year of experience I am a passionate and highly skilled web developer with a deep love for everything related to web technology My journey into the world of web development started when I was a high school student. Since then, I have honed my skills and gained valuable experience in creating stunning and functional websites and web applications.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Fontend Development

2023 to recent

Developer at fiver 2022 to 2023

Developer at freelancer.com 2022 to 2023

SKILSS

Web Development

Web design

App Development

